{
  "type": "fill_in_the_blank",
  "title": "Fill in the Blank (1 point each)",
  "instructions": "Type the correct answer(s) in the blank(s). Do NOT use periods to end your answers.",
  "points_per_question": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "___ was Atari's first hit game.",
      "answers": [["pong"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Established in 1860, ___ is the oldest game company in the US.",
      "answers": [["milton bradley","miltonbradley"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "In 1981 the US saw the arrival of Shigeru Miyamotoâ€™s arcade game named ___.",
      "answers": [["donkey kong","donkeykong","dk"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "___ was created by Gary Gygax and Dave Arneson created in 1973.",
      "answers": [["dungeons and dragons", "d&d","dnd","dungeons & dragons","d & d"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "UX stands for ___",
      "answers": [["user experience","userexperience","user exp","userexp"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The ___ hugely revitalized the video game industry in 1986.",
      "answers": [["nintendo entertainment system","nintendoentertainmentsystem","nes","famicom"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Gamers who score high on the ___ cluster want to finish everything the game has to offer and stive for power in the context of the game world.",
      "answers": [["achievement"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "In MDA, ___ refers to the moment to moment elements of player interaction.",
      "answers": [["mechanics"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The  ___ state, also known as 'The Zone', is characterized by complete absorption in what one does.",
      "answers": [["flow"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The first console wars in the US were between companies ___ and ___.",
      "answers": [["nintendo","sega"], ["nintendo","sega"]]
    }

  ]
}